pardon me.
What made that feel like meat and
potatoes is something that I usually
like to get to is
because it's so central
to what I do.
It connects to the right people. It
covers the right topics.
Hi.
You're smiling. You've seen him here
before. Hey. Um, if information is
nourishing, it's nourishing be this is
information was nourishing because it
was what I was specifically looking for.
It wasn't it wasn't a runaround. It
wasn't trying to find like I am now.
Where the devil did they put the
dishwasher soap? The sign on the sign
above the aisle says dish soap, but I
can't find any dish soap on this this
bucket aisle. So, uh, it wasn't that
kind of an experience. it doesn't feel
like the wires are getting jumbled, so
to speak.
It feels it feels like there's a there's
a connection been made. So that was, you
know, so I mean, so this week's been
pretty good.